hello everybody what is going on welcome
大家好，欢迎光临
to the third TV with python tutorial
到 python教程的第三台电视
basics video in this video we're going
基本视频在这个视频中，我们要去
to be talking about the key D language
要谈论的重点 d 语言
so this is where you might see these dot
所以这是你可能会看到这些 点的地方
K V files now it's actually the case
现在KV文件就是 这种 情况
that you don't ever need to use the key
你永远不需要 使用密钥
V language it's really there for just
V语言，它 真的就在那里
for you if that's what you want to use
对你来说，如果这就是你想要使用的
but you can actually write the identical
但你 实际上可以 写出相同的东西
application using pure Python code so as
应用程序使用纯Python代码，如
you can see here we've actually we've
你可以在这里看到我们实际上已经
utilized some key language only we've
只使用了一些关键语言
written it in pure Python but what you
用纯Python编写， 但是你的
can do is you can use these dot K V
可以做的是你可以使用这些点KV
files ah - maybe better organize your
文件啊 - 也许 更好的组织你的
presentation of the GUI and keep the
介绍的GUI和 保持
Python files for the logic so depending
Python文件的逻辑如此而定
on which way you think you might want to
你 认为 你可能想要 哪种方式
use our things separately but again it
分开使用我们的东西， 但它又一次
might actually be the case that your
实际上可能是你的 情况
application or your program is simpler
应用程序或您的程序更简单
if you keep it all together in just pure
如果你把它们全部放在一起纯粹
Python or if you're using a lot of
Python或如果您使用的是大量 的
customization or maybe you're using a
定制 或者你正在使用一个
lot of customization but a lot of that
很多的定制，但很多
customization is very redundant then it
定制是非常多余的 呢
would make a whole lot of sense to use
会使用很多意义
the K V files so I think you can get by
KV档案，所以我认为你可以通过
using you know doing one or the other it
使用你知道做一个或另一个
really doesn't matter but in programming
真的没关系，但在编程方面
in general there's a million different
一般来说有 一百万种不同的
ways to do something and everyone has
如何 做一些事情 ，每个人都有
their opinion on what the best way is
他们对 最佳方式的看法
and they'll ridicule you if you disagree
如果你不同意他们会嘲笑你
so I'll go ahead and show both versions
所以我会继续 并显示两个版本
here but honestly don't worry about what
在这里，但老实说，不要担心什么
other people say is the best just try
别人 说是 最好的尝试
and bolt out see what fits best to you
并拧出看看最适合你的东西
and use that so anyway that's what we're
并使用如此 反正这就是我们
going to cover here is the key V
这里要介绍的是关键的V
language so first I'm going to do is I'm
语言所以首先我要做的就是我
just going to go ahead and we'll get rid
只要继续前进，我们就会摆脱
of this we're not going to be using it
我们不打算使用它
for now and even we don't need these
现在 甚至我们 不需要这些
imports anymore either so this is kind
再也不输入任何东西， 所以这是实物
of one of our initial scripts only the
只有我们最初的脚本之一的
only difference here was this was label
唯一的区别 是 这是标签
and the parameter was text and it said
和参数是文本，它说
hello
你好
old worlds like this so save and run
像这样的旧世界如此保存和运行
that and that was our original
那和那是我们的原创
application if you recall so that's that
应用程序，如果你记得这样的话
and this is you know written in pure
这是你知道纯粹写的
Python now what if we wanted to write
Python的现在，如果我们想写
this in or at least utilize the keavy
这在或至少利用了重剑
language so what I'm going to do is I'm
语言，所以我要做的就是我
going to use notepad plus plus if you
如果你要使用记事本加plus
don't have it I highly suggest you get
没有它我强烈建议你得到
it you could write all this in just a
它可以把所有这一切都写入一个
regular notepad file and then use the
定期记事本文件，然后使用
same saving practices that we're about
与我们有关的相同的保存实践
to use but anyway so within your key V a
使用 但无论如何，这样你的钥匙 伏 内
file here what you can do is it's always
在这里文件你可以做的是它永远
a good idea to reference the file that
引用文件的 一个 好主意
you are kind of like associated with
你 有点像关联
because I have seen a second um the way
因为我 已经看到了第二个
that the Python script is going to know
该 Python 脚本会 知道
the dot K V file to use is really kind
使用的点KV文件真的很亲切
of screwy
的扭曲
I'm not quite sure why they went with
我不太确定他们为什么要这样做
the way that they went but they did so
他们去的方式，但他们这样做
anyway oh it's supposed to say you know
无论如何， 哦，它应该 说你知道
file name and this is going to be in
文件名，这将是在
conjunction with our a key B video three
我们的一个B键第三部影片结合
for example so key V video three pi put
例如关键V视频三个pi放
whatever your file name is you can
无论你的文件名是什么，你都可以
require a key V version here by using
通过使用 需要一个关键的V版本
the hash tag colon and then we can say
散列标签冒号 ，然后 我们可以说
key V one point 8.0 and that will also
关键V点 8.0，这 也将
put a requirement for the the key B
对关键B提出要求
language file so uh now let's kind of
语言文件 ，以便 呃 现在，让我们种
consult here we've got you know simple
在这里咨询我们已经 知道简单
key V app we've got a label and it says
关键V app 我们有一个标签 ，它说
text hello world so you can kind of
文本你好，世界，所以你可以种
envision your K V files now someone's
设想你的KV档案现在是某人的
going to like jump down my throat for
想要 跳下我的喉咙
this but dot K V files are a lot like
但这个点KV文件很像
CSS right so it's a lot like I having a
CSS的权利，所以这很像我有一个
stylesheet okay and so just like with
样式表可以，所以 就像
HTML and CSS you can kind of write you
HTML和CSS 你 可以写你
know text attributes right in the
知道正确的文本属性
paragraph tags let's say for example and
段落标签让我们说， 例如和
you can give kind of some style
你能给 样 的一些样式
attributes to it or you can have a style
属性，或者你可以有一个风格
sheet that says hey everything with a
表单嘿，所有的一切
paragraph tag class article right looks
段落标签类文章右看起来
like X right looks like this or you can
像X 右看起来 像这样或者你可以
actually you don't even need a CSS sheet
实际上你 甚至不需要CSS 表格
you could always just create custom
你 总是可以创建自定义
styles as you went like we can see with
如你所见的样式， 就像我们可以看到的一样
websites it makes a whole lot of sense
它使网站变得非常 有意义
to have a style sheet so you don't have
有一个样式表， 所以 你不必
to
至
continuously keep using classes now with
不断继续使用类与现在
applications depend on the application
应用程序取决于应用程序
if you have a small application or you
如果你有一个小应用程序 或你
don't have a lot of redundancy it's
没有 很多的冗余它
sometimes that actually I think is a
有时候，实际上 我认为是
little simpler to use it within the
简单 一点 到 内使用
application at least for me but again it
至少对我来说至少应用它
doesn't matter which one you use both of
不要紧 ，你同时使用的哪一个
them are very effective and both of them
他们是非常 有效的， 他们 两个
will work in the way that you expect
将以您期望 的方式工作
them to so anyways this is a kb file TV
他们这样反正这是一个 kb文件电视
requirement now how would we do this
现在要求 我们 如何 做到这一点
well like a CSS stylesheet first you're
就像你最初的CSS样式表一样
going to have you know the attribute so
会让你 知道属性
to speak so for us it's going to be we
为我们说话，这将是我们
want to say label now but this is
现在想说标签，但这是
basically it's a parent okay so this is
基本上这是一个父母好，所以这是
referencing any time we use labels so
参考我们任何时候使用标签的情况
that's referencing right here but you
这是在这里引用，但你
could take it a step further and add
可以 把它 更进 了一步 ，并 添加
other attributes within here we are
我们在这里的其他属性
going to do that but you could actually
要做到 这 一点 ，但 实际上 你 可以
have a button or like other stuff within
有一个按钮或其他内容
here there would be a child all the
这里会有一个小孩
labels so every child of a label with X
用X 标记标签中的 每个孩子
attribute would be a certain way but
属性会是某种方式，但是
anyway not to get too far ahead of
无论如何不要 过于 遥遥领先
ourselves I will show that when we get
我们自己，当我们得到时 ，我会表明
there but anyway so label 1 2 3 4 just
但无论如何， 所以标签 1 2 3 4只是
use the same kind of indentation
使用相同类型的缩进
practices and then you can have your
实践，然后你可以拥有你的
actual values here so text we're saying
实际值在这里，所以我们说的文字
text colon and then we can say hello
文字冒号 ， 然后我们可以 打招呼
world like this now that's it well it's
像这样的世界现在就是这样
all we're going to add right this
所有我们要添加这个
instant and what we can do now is we'll
瞬间， 我们现在可以做的 是 我们会
go file save as and I'm going to save
将文件另存为，我将保存
mine um we'll go save file type as and
我的嗯，我们会去保存文件类型为和
go to the very top and we'll say all
去最高层， 我们会说全部
types so this gets saved here is like
所以这里得到保存的类型就像
all types like that and then what we're
所有类型都是这样，然后我们是什么
going to do is we're going to save this
要做的是我们要保存这个
as a simple key v dot K V okay so hit
作为一个简单的关键v点K V没关系，所以命中
save and then instead of return label
保存，然后代替返回标签
and then specifying an attribute let's
然后指定一个属性让我们
just say return label so there's nothing
只是说退货标签，所以没有什么
else there so we'll save that and let's
否则，我们将保存它， 让我们
go ahead and run that and see if we work
继续 并运行， 看看我们的 工作
no we didn't work hold on let's see what
不，我们不努力，让我们看看是什么
says
说
apparently simple caveat okay well I
显然简单的告诫好吧，我
guess I didn't want us to be all cat or
我猜我 不想让 我们成为猫或者猫
to do camel casing let's go
做骆驼套让我们走吧
where here it is okay so it was yelling
在这里它是好的，所以它是大喊大叫
at me for the camel casing so I'm gonna
在我身上的骆驼套，所以我会去的
on camel case here so simple kv or
在骆驼案例这里 如此简单的KV或
simple ki v under like all under case so
下像所有简单き 五之下的情况下，使
I called it capitalize cap okay for some
我把它称为帽子 好的一些
reason it didn't like that I don't call
它不喜欢我不打电话的原因
that being an issue before man I still
这仍然是人类面临的一个问题
getting angry at me simple TV I'm
生我的简单电视就生我的气
looking at it man I don't know why
看着它的男人我不 知道为什么
you're telling me you can't find it
你告诉我你找不到它
seems there's a fist ups and takes
似乎有一个拳头 ups和采取
lessons TV / simple TV oh it's not dot
教训电视/简单的电视哦，它不是点
oh okay a simple TV now I'm gonna go
哦，好吧， 现在我要去 一个简单的电视
back I had used apparently a let's try
回来我显然使用过，我们试试吧
this one more time okay save and run
这一个更好的时间 保存并运行
that there we go okay so that's that's
我们会好起来的， 所以就是这样
why okay so the the problem was actually
为什么好， 所以问题实际上是这样
instead of dot K V I hit comma K V
而不是点KV 我打逗号KV
apparently so the camel casing was fun I
显然这样骆驼套很有趣我
just reverted it back to the camel
只是把它还给了骆驼
casing actually so now you can see we
现在的套管现在你可以看到我们了
have our application hello world just
有我们的应用程序的Hello World 只是
the same as it was before it's just now
与之前 的情况 一样
we're referencing this label now before
我们现在正在引用这个标签
we move too much further I do want to
我们 想要进一步 移动得 更远
show that
表明这一点
this one yeah there's the comma it's
这一个是啊有 它的 逗号
kind of really hard to see actually it
实际上很难看到它
is a comma I'll just say no there and
是一个逗号， 我只会在那里说不
let me open this up one last time and
让我开这件事最后 一次 和
interestingly enough the quv language is
有趣的是， quv语言是
kind of like a I don't know hybrid of
有点像我 不认识的混血儿
Python almost and so what you can
几乎是 Python， 所以你 可以
actually say is text equals hello world
实际上说的是文本等于你好世界
but what if we said text equals for
但是，如果我们所说的文本等于 为
example hello world and hello plus space
例如hello world 和hello plus space
world let's say so we'll save that and
世界让我们这么说，我们将保存 和
we'll run it and you still see that we
我们会运行它，你仍然看到我们
have the exact same hello world but then
有完全相同的问候世界， 但然后
what we can do is we can go in further
我们能做的是我们可以进一步走下去
and we can do hello world and comma 1
我们可以做你好世界 和逗号1
plus 1 super get away with that we're an
再加上1个超级玩家，我们就是这样
untested territories at the moment I got
在我得到的那一刻未经测试的领土
angry okay uh only accepts the string
生气好吧呃只接受字符串
okay that's fine so anyway we'll come
好吧 ，这很好 ，无论如何我们会来
back over here so that was actually a
回到这里，这实际上是一个
parameter issue so let's just do string
参数问题， 所以我们只是做字符串
1 plus 1 let's see if we get away with
1 加1让我们看看我们是否 逃避
that version at least still angry with
该版本至少仍然生气
me
我
source I converted it to a string you
我将它转换为一个字符串你
make me very angry um okay well
让我很生气嗯还好 好
apparently with our text labels it's
显然与我们的文字标签是一样的
very stringent as far as uh that it just
非常严格，只要它就是这样
wants text elements only but when you're
只需要文本元素， 但是当你的时候
not let's say you're not using the text
不要说你不使用文本
element you can actually incorporate
元素， 你可以实际 纳入
Python logic on the other side of the
Python 的另一边的逻辑
colon so at least you can see here with
所以至少你 可以在这里看到冒号
the plus we've incorporated some Python
我们加入了一些Python
logic but again this one's very
逻辑，但又是这个
stringent in it only wants text but
严格的只是想要文字而已
maybe later I'll show you guys some
也许以后我会告诉你们一些
actual logic within our keavy language
我们的 重要语言中的实际逻辑
here but like I said I think the only
在这里， 但像我 说的我认为唯一的
reason you would use this dot KB is
你会 使用这个点的原因是KB
strictly to actually separate the logic
严格地将逻辑分开
and make the keavy file just
并制作keavy文件
presentation
介绍
and the Python file just logic but
而Python 文件只是逻辑而已
anyway that's that so if you guys have
无论如何，这就是如此，如果你们有
any questions or comments please feel
任何问题或意见， 请感受
free to leave them below otherwise as
免费将他们留下， 否则如下
always thanks for watching things for
总是感谢你收看东西
all the supported subscriptions
所有受支持的订阅
until next time
直到下一次